{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"5.94/5.4",
			"answer":"5.94/5.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.356/8.9",
			"answer":"0.356/8.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"49.5/0.33",
			"answer":"49.5/0.33",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/70",
			"answer":"630/70",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.64/1.6",
			"answer":"4.64/1.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"86.18/3.1",
			"answer":"86.18/3.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.064/0.86",
			"answer":"2.064/0.86",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"64.96/5.6",
			"answer":"64.96/5.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2850/50",
			"answer":"2850/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"756.5/0.85",
			"answer":"756.5/0.85",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4140/4.6",
			"answer":"4140/4.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"90.71/4.7",
			"answer":"90.41/4.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.614/0.73",
			"answer":"8.614/0.73",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.3738/1.4",
			"answer":"0.3728/1.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3520/3.2",
			"answer":"3520/3.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}



	]
}